final List<Map<String, dynamic>> flutterQuiz = [
  {
    'question': 'What is Flutter?',
    'options': ['Framework', 'Library', 'Language', 'IDE'],
    'correctAnswer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Who developed Flutter?',
    'options': ['Apple', 'Google', 'Facebook', 'Microsoft'],
    'correctAnswer': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which language is used to write Flutter apps?',
    'options': ['Java', 'Kotlin', 'Dart', 'Swift'],
    'correctAnswer': 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What widget is used for layouts in Flutter?',
    'options': ['Container', 'Row', 'Column', 'All of the above'],
    'correctAnswer': 3,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is a state management approach in Flutter?',
    'options': ['Provider', 'Redux', 'Bloc', 'All of the above'],
    'correctAnswer': 3,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What does the “hot reload” feature in Flutter do?',
    'options': [
      'Restarts the app',
      'Applies code changes without restarting',
      'Builds the app',
      'None of the above'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the base class for all Flutter widgets?',
    'options': ['StatefulWidget', 'StatelessWidget', 'Widget', 'BuildContext'],
    'correctAnswer': 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the purpose of the Scaffold widget in Flutter?',
    'options': [
      'Provides structure for a basic material design layout',
      'Manages state',
      'Adds animations',
      'Handles navigation'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which widget is used to scroll content in Flutter?',
    'options': ['ScrollView', 'ListView', 'Column', 'PageView'],
    'correctAnswer': 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the default root widget in a Flutter app?',
    'options': ['AppBar', 'Scaffold', 'MaterialApp', 'Container'],
    'correctAnswer': 2,
  },
];
